A boat beneath a sunny sky,
Lingering onward dreamily
In an evening of July.
Children three that nestle near,
Eager eye and willing ear,
Pleased a simple tale to hear.
Long has paled that sunny sky,
Echoes fade and memories die,
Autumn frosts have slain July.
Ever drifting down the stream,
Lingering in the golden gleam,
Life, what is it but a dream?
Let's race again today!
What the hell are you doing?!
Watch where you're aiming!
Today's the day I finally get those idiots.
Those damn "outers" think they're on a tourist trip.
I'm through letting them get the best of me.
Roger that, Doctor Shouko!
Hey, this is a private communications channel!
You've given me a great workout every morning,
so I thought I should say thanks!
You make me so mad!
Bring back that hammer!
That's for Bishamaru!
How many was that?
Thirty one.
Damn it! I'm not done yet!
Sure I'll bring it back. If you make me a new one!
Do you have no shame?!
'Scuse us!
Thanks for the food.
Those children are always so lively.
Sis!
How's it going?
Only some boring small fries! I'm getting bored.
Shouko-chan, send out Bishamaru already!
No way! That thing's priceless!
You're so stingy.
They're so obstinate.
What are you looking at?
What is it you're doing?
I bet I know!
You're doing "it"!
The sun's barely up and you're already off to chase after another girl?
I'll make it up to you soon.
Oh, really? I wonder if that's true...
Have I ever lied to you?
Pretty fireworks!
They never seem to get tired of it.
That's enough.
Truly, everyday is like a carnival.
Wait! Wait!
What are you doing you stupid children?!
You're heading straight into Yase's no-go zone!
Sis...
Guess that'll call for a written apology.
No! It's not my fault! It's those three's fault!
Okay!
Special Technique!
See you tomorrow!
Nice shot!
You think Shouko's pissed off?
She's always pissed off.
Well, anyway...
That's another victory for us today-
We're leaving.
Welcome back.
I hope all three of those idiots die!
CAPITAL CRAZE
Are you listening?!
Look, I know you're tired,
but would you pay attention?
Yeah, no problem.
Sorry! Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
You'd better be sorry!
I'm begging you here! Do you hear me?
We got a little out of control 'cause it's a festival day.
That's right.
Don't lie to me!
There's a festival going on every day in your heads!
What?!
Hmph! Dummy! Poophead! Manslut Monk!
Shut up, you trio of idiots!
Un, you tell him off, too!
Let him have it!
Gotta pee.
Bad?
Gonna pee my pants.
What did you do until now?
Hold it in.
You weirdo!
Next time you do that, no food for three days.
That's child abuse.
Hurts me as much as it hurts you.
And clean up that room.
We just go exploring every day...
You always get so mad, Myoue.
Plastic Model
I'm just telling you to stop provoking people for no reason.
And here, we call that "breaking things," not "exploring."
For how much longer will I have to put up with the cultural differences here?
Just wait until we find the rabbit...
Okay?
Aren't you happy? Now you can go home.
Take the kids and get out.
Here.
Food! Food! Food!
It's nice to see the four of you getting along so well.
Honestly, they're so noisy, I can't stand it.
No candy during meals!
How can you look so glum on a happy day like this?
Things seem to be going well.
I've been sent a trio of evil spirits. They're haunting me.
Sorry to hear that!
...I guess I should say.
What's the problem? They seem to like him.
I'm jealous.
You can have the rights to the cake plate any time you want it.
Hmph! No, thanks.
Don't be like that. Our decisions here are absolute.
Correct?
Right, right.
I know that.
That girl is quite a handful, though.
More like three handfuls!
I like her! She's a tomboy! And so cute.
I have high hopes for her.
I don't think of them as evil spirits.
But playing pretend has always been a specialty of yours, right, Myoue?
Not nearly as much as you, Yase Douji.
From what I recall, the two of you were an even match.
So you're going to pretend you're not a part of this, Kurama?
You've been the master complainer for a long time.
Let's stop messing around.
If she hears us, there'll be a nasty scolding.
The day of our reunion draws near.
I can't wait! I'm so excited.
I don't know. She's a little kid who's absolutely useless.
If she can play with the toys, she has everything it takes.
She ain't a queen though.
What's wrong with that if she can become one!
Give her too much attention and she'll bite your hand off.
You're scared.
You've always been a crybaby.
Unlike you, I've grown out of my kid clothes.
Yet you need help getting into the adult clothes you wear?
Don't worry.
You're both equally little boys.
Anyway, that doesn't change the fact that this is a day to remember.
Let's have a splendid celebration.
Then let us swear to the "first," my siblings.
That between us, the "next three"...
...there be honor...
...and no secrets.
To obey the Ten Flawless Commandments,
in our name, and the name of our great mother!
We're heading out!
Koto.
Call my cell if anything happens.
Okay.
Is it wrong to pick a flower?
But it feels wrong to just let it wither...
Kifune-chan from "Miyakoi!" was captured.
Don't try to play dumb.
I've been thinking it was weird all morning.
I've told you numerous times, if you're going to do something, tell me first!
So what are you planning, monk?
Now, now, no more crying.
When will you come back?
Let me see... I'll have to ask.
No!
It's selfish.
Make sure not to fight, you three.
I'm sure we'll see each other soon.
How long are you going to cry for?
I give! I give!
We are selling talismans warding against evil.
We will not sell them tomorrow. They are available tonight only.
Faithful guest, take one and go home.
Light one candle as an offering.
Will you take one candle?
Your offering...
Don't worry. Any god who decides things based on the amount of the offering is a fake.
Whose shrine is this anyway?
Miyako-sama! It's Miyako-sama's shrine.
I don't know the details...
I think they're some important historical figure?
Right? Hey, put that game away!
No clue!
I think you pray for safe travels here?
I heard you can pray for whatever you want.
No! No! No! I mean my granny...
They've got ears... ears like this! Right?
And giant breasts!
Like a rabbit, right?
Miyako-sama? Oh, you mean Koto-sama.
I guess people of this day and age might not know her.
If you were to go inside the building today,
you might be able to see her.
This beauty is Koto-sama.
She left a long time ago. And she hasn't come back.
Now, over there-
We might not be able to go back.
Hey, what are you saying?
That's right! I mean, Koto-sama has to be the rabbit!
A-chan!
We don't know that yet!
But this is the first time we've seen a black rabbit!
Maybe the painting's good enough?
That's right!
But we didn't get to go home!
So we're stuck here, I think.
Jeez,
You two!
If you're stingy with your offerings, your prayers won't be answered.
They say money can buy you out of hell.
So we're in hell.
What? You didn't know that?
You're horrible, Koto. There's a demon here.
And a buddha, too.
Does it really matter if we can't go home?
Yase!
Koto! You were quite the tomboy this morning, weren't you?
You were watching?
Of course.
I'm a fan of yours.
You think she wants to see her parents, maybe?
Her parents, huh?
I've come to get you.
I'd be mad if we didn't get to see Koto anymore.
I bet her parents feel the same way. Probably.
What are you talking about?
Huh? Whaaaat?
We should've used this sooner.
It's lame, though. Not my style.
What? Are we doing something?
A lovely birthday party. And you're the star!
Koto!
What?!
Welcome to the Council of Three. We greet you.
What do you think you're doing, you two?
I told you, we're having a big celebration.
How can you have a birthday party without the birthday girl?
Um...
Today isn't my birthday.
Oh, my.
You're lying.
Damn it all.
Ever since you came back...
Every day's been a festival of light and sound.
Wait a second, no!
I haven't come back home! — I want to go home!
Yo! The latest issue of Saitou News!
Is the Koto of Kyoto the Koto of the Mirror Capital!!?
What the hell is going on?
You don't like it? Then...
Is the Koto of the Mirror Capital the Rabbit of the Mirror Capital!!?
Is the Koto of Kyoto actually Kyoto!!?
What the hell?!
Is the Koto of the Mirror Capital the Rabbit of Kyoto!!?
No! No! Not a chance!
Accepted artwork
Accepted
artwork
I don't even have boobs!
That's right.
What's important is what's inside.
Indeed.
All those with wishes come here.
Your Tanabata wish has been granted: advance 5 spaces.
This is the Capital after all.
Full moon night. Ill omen of misfortune: go back 10 spaces.
Wasn't it the Mirror Capital?
Carpe diem!
You had too much fun: miss the next turn.
It is the Malice Capital.
Crazy
This is the Crazy Capital...
Sutra
The Holy Capital...
Border
The Borderlands Capital...
Kyoto... Kyoto...
This is really confusing!
There must be purpose in even the smallest joke.
But can a simple child really be useful?
We would like to stake something on your childish potential.
This is some crazy game you're playing.
That's pretty much the point of Bishamaru.
Goodbye, Koto.
Stop it!
I haven't agreed to this.
I refuse to accept this as the Council's decision.
Obey the "first" and the rules, Kurama!
This is an official examination. You understand that, don't you?
You want to see Mom, too, don't you, Oedipus?
Mom?
I was getting so tired of waiting.
Perhaps I was right, and taking action ourselves is the quickest way to bring about our reunion.
A: It's Sis!
Un: We can't get out.
You understand, don't you, Koto?
Those idiots are having a party.
What do we do, Inari?
Well, I think a person's appearance counts for something.
And I'm not your mom, either.
But I know how it feels to want to see your family.
So I'll play along with you. Just this once.
No! Don't!
What an obstinate man.
Damn it. Get the fuck out of my damn way, demon!
How are you going to make me, human?!
Y'know, you guys have been really good to me.
But you know, Head Priest...
You shouldn't push your expectations on kids.
Moral of the story, don't trust adults.
Guess this has to get ugly.
Wait, damn it!
You look Iike an idiot, getting so angry.
I'll shut you up right now, demon!
That's quite a case of sibling rivalry.
A      Why can't she crush it?
Un    He's cheating!
A     Using cheat characters isn't fair!
Look at you now, Princess.
You stupid human!
Man, you're pissing me off.
But what about this?
A      Do it, Koto!
Un    Aye, finish off yonder thing!
Hey, Myoue. There's something I've always wanted to ask you.
Every time you open your mouth, it's nothing but complaints.
But you treat those children like they're your treasures.
Nothing is supposed to be a secret between us... Tell me, Myoue.
Which one of them are you going to miss the most?
Take that, toaster!
Special Move:
Home Appliance Slaughterer!
Idiot.
Idiot...
Hold on a second! Time out! Time out!
Maybe it was a waste after all.
Are you sure about this?
A     Let us out!
Let's wait and see.
Un     Let us out!
A     Let us out! Let us out!
Un     Let us out! Let us out!
Shouko-san, are you feeling kind of down?
Ow! Ow! Ow! Come on, that hurts.
What a handful they are.
No matter how much they grow up, they keep fighting.
This is his fault for leaving them alone all this time.
But I'm happy to see you again!
I've been waiting for you this whole time, too.
A virus?
"Once I've said something, that's how it shall be."
Those words of yours are my power.
Look! It's Mom! It's Mom!
Sis!
Now, tell me, my king, my lord!
Your wish is my wish.
...want to...
I want to go home!
I'd even cut things off,
to prove the fact I exist.
Though eternal lies surround me,
they're my safety line.
"Wanna take you high?"
The galaxy shakes. You smile.
I want to touch you. I don't want
to hear that it's forbidden.
Moved to emotion by arguments,
I cast aside reason.
I enter a game of risk that's
devoid of reason.
It's resplendent with rare pain.
Mistaking the real for the unreal.
It transcends all understanding.
Koto!
So, fight!
You've gotten so pretty, Princess.
Oh my, and you grew up so fast, Kurama!
And you are as beautiful as ever, Koto.
Thank you.
I got kissed by a woman! A woman kissed me!
Poor you.
Look at how you've grown! Can you sleep alone now, Myoue?
Shut up.
And look at all the children you have!
They ain't mine!
Koto.
I'm sorry.
It seems I misunderstood.
Can we put it behind us?
Go on.
I'm happy you were able to return, Koto-sama.
You were waiting for someone to come for you, right?
Welcome home!
I don't really get it though.
Me neither.
I'm home.
So, fight!
Save
Don't Save
Now we'd like to go home too, please.
Why?
Koto, you can't go home anymore.