Once upon a time, when the countless worlds bordered on each other,
and the line between god and human was vague,
there was a certain family whose story of love and rebirth we will follow.
Sometimes my love rises
to cheer me up
This here is all I have
Even the rain is beautiful
The droplets dance
like the rain
Everything is so much fun here
A world of music
I feel like I've started
to listen to everyone
with a smile
I can accept this place as my home
Let's say goodbye
Night falls to draw me in
This wild world
turns to link us
It turns so we can
meet and laugh once more
Sensei, how are you?
I'm sorry I just disappeared.
Are you worried about me?
Are you nuts?!
Die in a fire!
I'm in the Mirror Capital now.
Welcome, Little Sister
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
Chapter Four
Past (4) /
Shrine Monk A
I have to get going.
Okay.
You look so gloomy!
What a moody little brat!
Hey, now.
Central Axis
General Agency
Shrine
It won't be long.
Okay.
Thanks.
Watch the place while I'm gone, okay
Okay.
Tell the priests if something happens, okay?
What else...
Count your tears, crybaby!
Inari won't be around to save you, wimp!
Stop it, you two.
Familiars aren't capable of ill-will.
Don't worry about what they say.
You're a member of the Shrine now. Keep your head held high,
Planetary General
Agency Shrine
no matter what they say.
Okay, Sensei.
So the child the Fox took is one of us now?
How impudent.
It's a disgrace.
I have no idea what that Fox is thinking.
Who knows if that child is a human or a monster...
Those red eyes...
Don't skip your training.
Get stronger and face them head-on.
I'm sure that's what your mom would say, Koto.
Just do the best you can, shrimp!
We'll play with you when we get back.
Take care!
It's Koto, run!
Shouldn't we stop Koto-chan?
Koto!
Keep your arms closer to your body when you punch.
Okay!
There's something wrong with that student and her teacher!
These acts are not worthy of one who would wear the fox mask!
High Priest, I beg you to address this problem directly...
Inari! Koto!
You heard him, yes?
Yes! I think it's their fault for messing around during training.
And for not apologizing.
And for being weak.
You seem a little stressed out to me.
Might I suggest you take a vacation?
I'll take care of your students while you're gone.
What?! No! No! No! No! I don't want you to do that, Sensei!
But this teacher is having doubts about his teaching methods.
No! No! No! No!
Someone has to lend him a hand.
This isn't about me!
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Chapter Five
Past (5) /
Shrine Monk B
Koto
Good morning, Koto.
Good morning!
I have a secret.
You're sleeping with your mask on again.
You're so weird.
Koto...
Morning!
Morning, you tomboy.
This place is so big, Sensei.
Isn't it nice to have so many rooms?
So bitter!
Horrible...
Should we look up all the harmful stuff in burned bread?
Don't waste your day.
What's your problem, guys?
Sensei, you're pretty useless outside your job, huh?
You wound me.
Wonder if I should start cooking again.
Not a chance.
Just put some sugar on if you think it's too bitter.
Over my dead body!
Where are you going today?
To assist the observers.
Just assist?
What's wrong with that?
When are you changing plane?
Nine o'clock, I think...
Time to stay in school
Don't rush me, Koto!
Might have to work all night!
Hurry up, fox!
Take... care...
Koto!
I knew you'd be here.
I was looking for you.
Katsura?
I can tell you've forgotten.
A checkup!
Bingo.
I forgot! Sorry!
Sorry! I forgot!
Sorry!
Koto...
I have a secret.
Inari's on bodyguard duty all day?
Such a waste.
You could put a special unit to much better uses.
Even the head priest watches his step when he deals with the old families.
I heard you got into a fight with some noble kids.
I didn't.
Nobody'd call that a real fight.
Hey!
I like that, Koto!
That's the spirit! Beat your way through!
He must be stupid.
He must be.
That hurt, dammit!
You messed up my vision just now!
You trying to kill me?
You can't die, Ichijouji.
That's not the issue!
Out of my face!
What if you damaged the data?!
You worry about that now?
What do you mean?!
She's got a point.
What?!
You should have it checked out.
Katsura...
Koto!
You always get along so well.
Head Priest!
I recommend Koto for an early combat assignment.
I have been amply assured of her willingness!
Ichijouji's just weak.
Damn you!
Is that so?
I expect much of you, disciple of the fox.
Sure!
Your prowess delights me.
However, you shouldn't neglect your studies.
And you! Don't spoil her!
Nothing of the sort.
It's too late anyway.
I get the complaints if she skips class.
Geez, you just can't get used to school, can you?
Shrine is trusted with protecting the order of this world,
and has done so since ancient times with pride and skill.
Koto! Koto!
23         Sakaki Yuuta
24      Hinohara Enishi
25               Koto
Fang!
Grand!
Dung!
G again?!
Get ready for the last fight of your life!
I thought you fled from me, Koto!
Hachiman...
Today I shall defeat you!
You said that yesterday too.
Silence!
Fight me!
Come at me!
Are you making fun of me?!
I don't have anything else with me.
You think you can defeat me using that?!
Yeah.
Fine!
Once more!
Once more...
Once... more...
Just give up.
A valiant effort.
Let me die a man's death!
Nope.
Damn it!
Deal with it.
Shut up!
A man of the Hachiman family won't accept defeat!
This brings shame to our name!
Living the tough life of a noble.
Shut up!
Don't cry.
You used to cry so much!
Then one day you just toughened up.
The hell are you?
Come on, Hachiman.
Everyone knows.
I'm the foundling of the fox.
Hey!
Good luck fighting for your family!
That's not what I meant!
And tomorrow you're eating dust!
Yeah, sure.
Welcome home, Koto!
Good to be back home!
There it is!
Koto
Mom...
Sensei...
Sensei?
Koto
Koto...
Koto?
I have a secret.
Welcome back!
I'm home.
When did you arrive?
Just now.
And you?
Just now!
What is it?
I thought you were asleep.
I was awake!
What?
Koto?
Did you cry today, Dad?
Huh?
We have a secret.
Still she haunts me, phantomwise,
Alice moving under skies
Never seen by waking eyes.
Children yet, the tale to hear,
Eager eye and willing ear,
Lovingly shall nestle near.
In a Wonderland they lie,
Dreaming as the days go by...
Good morning!
You're mumbling to yourself again.
Mumbling?
You were thinking about the Mirror Capital again, weren't you?
I wonder.
You're always lying!
I know it!
Ouch!
That was a good kick. You put your weight into it.
I suppose I should praise you for training hard.
Of course!
I'm going to be number one at the Shrine!
The crybaby I knew sure has grown up.
As a teacher, I'm very proud.
I might end up being stronger than you.
I guess you'll be the teacher, then!
I want to go find Mom.
I want to meet her and talk to her.
I hope she's pretty.
I'm sure she'll be surprised.
I want to ask her about Dad, too.
But, Sensei, you already know the truth, right?
Yeah.
Koto, I'm sure you'll make it there one day.
Where summer dies and is born anew.
Paradise lost.
The place beyond the mirror, where the gravestones of memories stand in neat rows.
I know you will.
Chapter Six
Present (2) / Council of Three
I was wondering why you bothered to show up for once.
Look at your face.
Things seem to be going well.
I've been sent a trio of evil spirits.
They're haunting me.
Sorry to hear that!
...I guess I should say.
What's the problem?
They seem to like him.
I'm jealous.
You can have the rights to the cake plate any time you want it.
Hmph! No, thanks.
Don't be like that.
Our decisions here are absolute.
Correct?
Right, right.
I know that.
That girl is quite a handful, though.
More like three handfuls!
I like her! She's a tomboy! And so cute.
I have high hopes for her.
She has the same name and the same red eyes.
Are you telling me she's her?
I wonder.
You're scared.
You've always been a crybaby.
Unlike you, I've grown out of my kid clothes.
Yet you need help getting into the adult clothes you wear?
Don't worry.
You're both equally little boys.
There is no arguing either way that she is special.
Let us welcome our first unlikely guest since they left us.
Then let us swear to the "first," my siblings.
That between us, the "next three"...
...there be honor...
...and no secrets.
To obey the Ten Flawless Commandments,
in our name, and the name of our great mother!
I'm there, Dad.
Sharp as a knife
I want to prove my own existence
Infinity stretches out around me and yet that is my safety line
Wanna take you high
The galaxy shines as you smile
I want to touch you
I don't want to listen to my punishments
Logic overwhelms me and I throw away reason
to sign up for this unreasonable risk game
I shine brightly thanks to expectations and pain
but I can't tell real and unreal apart
Fight with all your knowledge
So fight
When Mother and Father disappeared, I didn't cry.
My brother and sister cried quite a lot,
but I was determined to hold my ground in the wide world.
That's how I could prove my worth.
The Firstborn and His
Cheerful and Nerdy Team
Next time: "The Firstborn and
His Cheerful and Nerdy Team".
That was the day the story began.