Once upon a time, when the countless worlds bordered on each other,
and the line between god and human was vague,
there was a certain family whose story of love and rebirth we will follow.
Sometimes my love rises
to cheer me up
This here is all I have
Even the rain is beautiful
The droplets dance
like the rain
Everything is so much fun here
A world of music
I feel like I've started
to listen to everyone
with a smile
I can accept this place as my home, just as any other
Goodbye, Sun
Night falls to draw me in
We'll be fine, because this world
turns to link us
It turns so we can
meet and laugh once more
Everyone
has
their place
Everyone
has
their place
Everyone should know their place in this world. Monks are to be monks and commoners are to be commoners. Emperors are to be emperors and retainers are to be retainers. Disregarding one's place is evil.
Says
Priest
Myoue
from Toganoo
I do not claim I can ever reach the Pure Lands.
I merely desire to live this life as I am meant to.
from Toganoo
Father...
Mother...
The Youthful Youngest Child's Problems and the Beginning and the End
He's got a weird face.
Really ugly.
And he's drooling.
The hell are you doing here?
Say what?
You've woken up?
Thanks for the food!
Dig in.
What are they doing here?
We told you to make breakfast first if you're gonna be gone overnight!
You must have been hungry.
This's great!
Maybe we'll come back tomorrow.
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Chapter Thirteen
Present (8)/
Priest Myoue A
Celery
Juice
Hey, that's mine!
I ain't treating you! Cough up my dough!
Hey! You!
Answer me!
Come on!
You're gonna pay for this.
Celery
Juice
Let's take the day off.
Yuck!
Surely a single can of juice is nothing to get worked up about.
More importantly, why is one of us skipping the meeting to waste time?
He gets like this whenever this time of year comes around.
The train was empty again this year.
That's why.
He doesn't want us to see how depressed he is.
He gets his hopes up for no reason, and then thinks he's been betrayed.
You're quite harsh.
Well, he acts like he's the only one who's hurt!
It's the same for us!
Well, not exactly the same, which makes me even more mad.
The king has yet to return, and the old days are gone forever.
Come to think of it, there was a story I once heard.
About a dog waiting faithfully for his master to return.
The dog stands in the same spot, forever waiting.
But his master is long dead.
The dog doesn't know that, so he waits and waits and waits.
At long last, he finally tires of waiting, and dies.
Tragic, right?
Doesn't it make you want to cry?
Did the dog have no legs?
No bark to call his master?
No ears to listen?
If he did?
Then the dog was a fool.
Why do you say so?
His master never told him to die, right?
Hachiko
Would his master have been happy that he died waiting for him?
I see. An opinion that befits you.
I have my own opinion regarding this story.
Was the dog truly waiting for his master?
If so, would he not have acted differently?
But if the dog was waiting precisely for what came in the end...
Silence! Don't lampoon the dog's devotion! That's depressing!
How scary. How terrifying indeed.
Myoue!
Hey.
You floated away your stuff already?
Nah.
What about you?
You don't need that anymore?
That's why I'm floating it away.
I'm fine. I'll just buy new stuff.
I envy you.
I was thinking of taking up soccer.
Koto's really good at it.
Did you know?
No.
Myoue!
What are you doing here?!
Dodgeball.
Isn't that obvious?
Tell him we're investigating!
He's gonna give us the bead treatment if he finds out we're just playing.
We're investigating!
You're just playing.
Are you okay?
Is he dead? Myoue's dead?
The outside world doesn't make any sense either, but that's what makes it fun!
You're pulling my leg!
What a weird tale.
That's so like you, Koto.
I know she's weird.
I'm serious! Let's go there one day!
I'll take you to the outside world one day.
But...
I promise.
Looking forward to it.
Don't promise something you can't live up to.
You got in, but now you're just leeching off me!
All you're doing is screwing around, hoping something will change.
It looks to me like you just want to chill here.
What's wrong, Myoue?
Just looking at you pisses me off.
You're stupid, inconsiderate, and cheeky.
I always get the short end of the stick.
Nobody does anything but get in my way.
Just piss off already!
Myoue?
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Chapter Fourteen
Present (9)/
Priest Myoue B
Let me crash!
I'm sorry I just turned up,
but your boyfriend went nuts.
So you came here to get back at him?
You brought plenty of food too.
Try these.
You're a funny one, Koto.
Nobody else can piss him off like you can.
He gets pissed off all by himself just fine.
Maybe.
This is great!
He's always pissed off,
but earlier it was just...
He seemed like he was seriously angry with me.
I don't really get it.
I feel persecuted.
It's been a long time since he actually got mad.
I was getting the feeling he'd really calmed down.
He's been ditching work for a long time now.
I'm glad you came.
Help Myoue. Okay, Koto?
What are you talking about?
Please.
I'm the one in need of help here.
No sweat.
You're not making more sense than your boyfriend.
What shall we eat for dinner...
Want something in particular?
Meat or something?
Or something?
I'm sorry for forcing you to go along with my little game for so long.
This is the last selfish request I'll make of you.
I entrust the mantle of "Monk Myoue" to you.
Watch the place while I'm gone, okay?
One day I promise I will return with the beginning and end in tow.
I promise.
Wait for me,
Myoue.
Fine.
I guess it's your turn now.
Is she still here?
I wound up here because I read the sign wrong...
A child has to know its own direction, even if it has no name.
If you want to take that luggage on board, put the "fragile" sticker on it.
You read the sign wrong, so...
Never mind what you're told.
Just buy your ticket when the train stops.
I sure hope she's not trying to board the train.
Right?
Hey!
What's up, Inuyama-san?
What are you doing here?
Taking Myoue out for a walk?
Just kidding!
Come on, don't be mad, Myoue!
Waiting for a girl?
Drop it.
What about you? Why are you here?
Just trying to get a feel for the place.
I'm on my way home now, though.
Inuyama-san, did you come to get me?
That's so nice of you! Thanks!
What?
Nothing.
How about some food?
Chapter Fifteen
Present (10)/ The Two of Them
What's for dinner?
Fish!
Come on! I want meat!
Too fast!
Want me to drive?
No, thanks.
Come on, just for a little!
I said, "no"!
Bishamaru
the Peerless
A fiery spirit and punch!
A breathtaking adventure!
Premiere
Hey, hey.
A fiery spirit and punch!
A breathtaking adventure!
Can you please shut up?
What is your problem?
You said to shut up.
What is this place?
Almost everything's sold out.
Feels kind of sad...
Yeah.
Hey, didn't it ever occur to you to get on that train and see if it takes you home?
Oh, man! It never did!
You can be pretty smart, Myoue!
Can it!
I'll try next time it turns up.
Not now though.
I've got plenty to do.
Oh, really?
Can I go home now?
You can't!
You can go on your own, right? It's just a no-go zone.
No! If you don't come with me, I'll start smashing stuff.
A and Un are waiting.
I promised to go get them.
Myoue!
Right, right.
I won't smash stuff.
Better believe you won't.
I think A and Un are really cute! Aren't they?
They're the first...
relatives, or family, for me.
You don't care if they're not human like you?
Nope!
Normally that'd be relevant when accepting your family...
Couldn't you come up with better names for them?
Like Tarou and Jirou or something.
Those sound like old man names.
Huh?!
They do not!
The names they have are cool!
"A" and "Un" stand for the beginning and the end.
I...
think...
just understood...
Take this!
You were wide open!
You little... Wait, Koto!
Wait! Lemme give you a good beating!
Dummy, dummy!
Wait, you little...
What do you think you're doing?!
What?
I think that the black rabbit you're looking for is our mother.
I'll help you looking for her.
Let's adopt him!
Heavens! What happened?
I found him.
In exchange I want you to help me too.
There's a place I've wanted to go to for ages.
Once we find our mother,
please kill me.
Sharp as a knife
I want to prove my own existence
Infinity stretches out around me and yet that is my safety line
Wanna take you high
The galaxy shines as you smile
I want to touch you
I don't want to listen to my punishments
Logic overwhelms me and I throw away reason
to sign up for this unreasonable risk game
I shine brightly thanks to expectations and pain
but I can't tell real and unreal apart
Fight with all your knowledge
So fight
Kyoto's great!
Food's good, and parties everywhere.
So much fun...
Don't wanna go home...
The Assembly of the Three...
Preparing a party...
Yase and Kurama sneaking around...
Myoue moping by himself...
Big trouble! They're dragging Koto into this!
Plan of Two, Trouble of One
Next time: "Plan of two, trouble of one".
Stop wasting time.
Let's have fun...