Once upon a time, when the countless worlds bordered on each other,
and the line between god and human was vague,
there was a certain family whose story of love and rebirth we will follow.
Sometimes my love rises
to cheer me up
This here is all I have
Even the rain is beautiful
The droplets dance
like the rain
Everything is so much fun here
A world of music
I feel like I've started
to listen to everyone
with a smile
I can accept this place as my home, just as any other
Goodbye, Sun
Night falls to draw me in
We'll be fine, because this world
turns to link us
It turns so we can
meet and laugh once more
Hey, Kurama!
What's going on?
What if it stays like this?
What's happened to Koto?
What's going on?
A virus?
Look! It's Mom! It's Mom!
Sis!
Both Mother and Father Have Returned
Chapter Nineteen
Present (13)/ Reunion
Mom?
Koto?
Mom!
Mom, it's me! Koto!
I've been looking for you my whole life!
I'm here for you!
Are you...
really Koto?
I wanted to meet you so badly, Mom!
Me too, Koto.
Get lost!
There's a lot of stuff I'd love to ask you right here,
but let's go home first.
Everybody is waiting.
Koto! Koto! Koto!
Koto!
You've gotten so pretty, Princess.
Oh my, and you grew up so fast, Kurama!
And you're as beautiful as ever, Koto.
Thank you.
I thought I was gonna die there!
I thought I was gonna bite the dust!
Poor Koto.
Look at how you've grown!
Can you sleep alone now, Myoue?
Shut up.
And look at all the children you have!
They ain't mine!
I'm kidding.
Koto.
Mom?
Sorry. Your siblings put you through a lot, it seems.
Will you forgive them?
I'm so happy to see you, Mom.
Me too.
Welcome home!
I'm home.
Chapter Twenty
Present (14)/ Homecoming
Wow, the city's changed so much!
Look, it's Lady Koto.
Lady Koto!
We thank you.
The Council of Three.
You know...
we kinda stand out.
I see you all harmoniously kept watch over the Mirror Capital.
You're such good kids!
Mom! Let's go to the mountains!
I'll hold a tea party for you!
So you're in charge of the mountains, Yase?
Yeah!
And Myoue's in charge of slacking off.
No.
Then what?
Babysitting fills my entire schedule.
Could that possibly...
...refer to us?
The monk is being mean.
Who else'd I refer to?
I know you like us.
If we weren't here, you'd cry!
What a wimp!
Shut up, you idiots!
Did you come up with those, Kurama?
You're always so smart!
I want to see more!
So pretty! What are these?
A monitor.
A monitor?
Do the colors change if I push them?
You shouldn't touch it too much.
I shouldn't?
It's not a machine that changes colors.
So she's the mother of the Council?
She left before you arrived?
Yeah.
And she's my mom too!
You don't resemble her much.
Come on! We're totally similar.
Mother, I think that's enough.
What happened, all of a sudden?
You are similar!
What are you doing? Goddamn it!
Sorry.
We can skip my place.
Oh, come on!
There's nothing to see.
I wanna see everything!
You're so tidy!
So you like cooking?
Not really.
You're such a hardworking boy!
I share this room with A and Un.
I told you to clean up before you leave!
Please enjoy!
Thanks.
It's great!
Right?
It's the same tea that we drank back then.
You're right.
This brings back memories.
I'm surprised you kept all this.
It all reminds me of what we did together.
How could I throw it away?
I'm so happy you returned.
Yase...
I'm sorry I suddenly disappeared.
It's okay.
Don't worry about it, Koto.
This was lots of fun.
It's time for me to go back, I guess.
Why?
No!
Why would you?
We finally have you back!
It's enough that I know you're all doing well.
Also...
We said we'd be back together, but here I am...
He's gonna be mad at me.
Dad's gonna be back too! He is!
Yase...
Go back? How?
I'm not helping with that stuff again!
How did you get here in the first place?
Corporate secret!
You don't know how to get back, anyway.
Ouch!
Koto.
No!
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Chapter
Twenty One
Present (15) /
Difference / Koto
Mom!
Koto.
I'm sorry about the chaos.
Don't worry.
You've grown so much, Koto.
It's been so long.
When I saw you the last time you were a baby.
We met when I was a baby?
Of course.
You were this tiny.
We went there together.
Really?
I had no idea!
Dad didn't tell you anything?
He didn't seem to like the topic.
Or rather...
"You know, right? I don't have to talk about it."
Kinda like that.
Yeah, sounds like him.
He's always been like that.
There's no way I'd "know."
Your hair is as easy to comb as his.
Really?
Yeah.
My eye color too.
Yeah, that's the same too.
The same as yours, right?
Yeah.
There, there.
You really gonna go back there, Mom?
I know what that place is.
It's a Shrine sanctuary, right?
What were you doing there?
Koto...
Sensei and the people of Shrine wouldn't tell me anything.
But I wanna know more!
About myself, about Dad, about you.
I thought you were the monk when I saw you.
I thought he'd come for me like he promised.
That he'd come to live up to his promise, however late.
I guess the world isn't that simple.
Koto, can you save that poor man from the dream which traps him?
The hole your sister made has closed already.
The catalyst is out of our reach.
Is something the matter?
Something is bothering me...
How could she tell us she's "going back" so coolly?
It's time for me to go back, I guess.
How?
No!
What happened?
You're not staying there tonight?
Yeah.
This is my first time seeing this room.
Thiere's nothing in it, is there?
Your girlfriend never comes here.
She's not my girlfriend.
She's too good for me.
You keep going on about how everything's too something for you.
Don't get bored of it?
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Must be nice to be you.
You have a past to be upset over.
I'm jealous.
You have a past too.
No!
I don't.
I... only have a future.
I can only keep going if I want to understand anything.
Come on,
what's gotten into you?
Come on.
I won't know if you don't say anything.
Everyone... Everyone's keeps asking things of me!
Why?!
Koto?
I've got lots of things I want to ask too!
But no one tells me anything!
Calm down, Koto.
I've had it!
I have my own problems!
It's because you're special.
That's just how it is.
Sensei?
Well, you just have to get used to it.
Sensei... Sensei!
Are you crying again, wimp?
You're such a baby, shrimp.
It's been a while since I last saw you cry.
Sensei! Why are you and the cats here?
This is the Mirror Capital!
Yeah.
I know.
What was that?
Are you the head monk?
Long time no see,
Yakushimaru.
My mistake. You're
Head Monk Myoue now.
Sensei, how did you come here?
You guys were getting out of hand.
You idiots were having a party.
And it's made a mess for us.
I can't believe what you did, you little tomboy.
My dream turns real... But why now?
There can only be one explanation.
It wasn't me
that the Shrine feared and tried to hide.
What do you mean?
How did you get to the Mirror Capital?
There's no entrance anywhere,
so I opened one with Aratama.
You did, too. With your sword, right?
Judging from your reaction, there can be no mistake.
Good grief.
Nothing ever changes.
Our father brings all the trouble.
And our lovely little sister too, I suppose.
I found Mom too!
Aren't you glad, Sensei?
Sharp as a knife
I want to prove my own existence
Infinity stretches out around me and yet that is my safety line
Wanna take you high
The galaxy shines as you smile
I want to touch you
I don't want to listen to my punishments
Logic overwhelms me and I throw away reason
to sign up for this unreasonable risk game
I shine brightly thanks to expectations and pain
but I can't tell real and unreal apart
Fight with all your knowledge
So fight
Wait, the Mirror Capital's falling apart?!
Oh, crap!
This isn't funny!
Will we be all right?
But, well, the head priest has come too, so everything should work out!
Wait,
the cause of this whole mess
was me?
The Big Argument
Next time: "The Big Argument".
Are you even listening to me, Sensei?
What are we going to do now?