Once upon a time, when the countless worlds bordered on each other,
and the line between god and human was vague,
there was a certain family whose story of love and rebirth we will follow.
Sometimes my love rises
to cheer me up
This here is all I have
Even the rain is beautiful
The droplets dance
like the rain
Everything is so much fun here
A world of music
I feel like I've started
to listen to everyone
with a smile
I can accept this place as my home, just as any other
Goodbye, Sun
Night falls to draw me in
We'll be fine, because this world
turns to link us
It turns so we can
meet and laugh once more
We haven't learned a thing...
Have we?
Oh well.
The Big Argument
Chapter Twenty Two
Present (16)/ Destruction
What's going on?
Hey!
What is this?
Explain! Aren't you the head monk?
Myoue...
I did this...
This is happening because I broke in with Aratama...
Right, Sensei?
Hey.
Darling...
Oh, dear.
The Ouji North area has been destroyed.
We can't respond fast enough.
I'll do it!
No. 12 and 13!
What's going on?!
Hey!
Are you all right?
My granny... is gone...
The shrine too...
Did you lose something too?
Why are you talking like that?
Sis...
It's okay, Koto.
What do you mean, "it's okay"?
There's been massive damage, Koto!
What?
It's not Koto's fault!
Then whose is it?
This is all Koto's fault!
Shut up! Don't blame it all on Koto!
Yeah!
You wanna fight, kid?
You're gonna regret this.
Miss girlfriend!
Koto...
I'm glad...
What's up?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine. It's nothing serious.
The wound will be gone in no time.
And are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Koto?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm really sorry!
Why didn't you tell her anything?
Didn't I ask you to care for her when I left?
I'm quite sure I did!
And not just her! You didn't tell me either!
Why do you always just stand there and never say anything?
You knew my dream would change.
Don't be so angry...
After all this has happened...
After all this...
How can I not be angry?
But...
There's no "but"!
I'm sorry, okay?
Stop acting like that!
Jeez...
You're certainly not acting like you haven't seen each other in centuries.
That form.
Father, we are no children anymore.
Don't you think it's about time to explain?
Explain this catastrophe.
Explain the reason you left.
Explain Koto.
Head priest!
You see...
Yase Douji is at the station right now...
How nice! I can see people!
Yase?
What are you doing there?
Oh, hello.
Who are you?
You're so beautiful.
Yase...
It's affecting her memories already?
That's my girl!
Koto.
Our daughter is so... wonderfully special.
You okay, Koto?
Did you get hurt somewhere?
Really, what's the matter, Koto?
Sis?
This is all my fault.
Take this for now.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry I got you hurt.
Don't worry.
I'll do something about this.
I will! No matter what!
We've been waiting for this!
Here it is!
What's going on?
Oh, wow.
It's him...
Shrine...
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Chapter
Twenty Three
Present (17)/ Shrine
Why are Shrine people here?
We've got unwelcome guests!
Uh oh, they've found out about your paradise!
What do you mean?
What do we mean? Exactly what we said.
Inari's been keeping this a secret.
The location of this dream paradise.
But paradise is lost.
It's hard to keep secrets from Shrine.
And once they find out, that's it for the land of dreams!
What? What are you trying to say?
You're special, Koto.
A special little girl.
You were born from a god and a Buddha...
Some real divinity met there.
Why is the head priest here?
You don't know, do you, little girl?
The other side of the looking glass is a figment.
It's the thirteenth plane, not supposed to exist.
The thirteenth?
I didn't expect you so early.
How many years has it been since we met?
It's been a long time.
I would have preferred to meet under different circumstances myself.
Sadly, such fundamental accidents are difficult to deal with even for us.
This is a nice place, Inari.
I can understand your desire to hide it.
Great place, right?
I'd appreciate it if you'd just pretend you never found out about it.
Unfortunately...
Head priest!
Koto?
Why have you come in person?
I'm the one who's surprised, Koto.
You disappeared the day you were deployed,
only to pop up once in order to smash the control system in the sanctuary.
You and your parents are far too unpredictable for my taste.
Well, I did make it here before the end, thanks to you...
So I guess it worked out okay.
Hold on!
You just said "before the end", didn't you?
What do you mean?
You have no idea how worried Katsura was.
Head priest!
The Mirror Capital will end here.
That's horrible!
There aren't many options at this point.
Come on!
Ichijouji and the others might know something!
Please, head priest! I don't want to destroy this place!
Koto, some things—
Isn't it the job of the general agency to protect the stability and harmony of the world?!
I'm a member of your special squad too!
If you won't help, I'll do what I can alone!
Koto!
That's not acceptable.
There are some things we can't allow precisely because we're the general agency.
This place should never have existed.
The thirteenth plane...
Where did you hear that?
If you know, that makes things easier.
Your father disobeyed his orders to make this forbidden place.
Will you force me to tell it all?
Do your job, observer!
Observer?
Sensei?
This place, the capital in the mirror,
isn't just some picture world.
It's a plane I made and kept secret from Shrine.
I would have been in for trouble if I hadn't hid it so deftly.
I never thought you'd go so far,
Koto.
Ordinarily nobody would be able to force their way in.
But you, too—
I only got in because you opened a way from this side.
Once space is sufficiently warped,
it's quite simple, really.
Whom does she take after, I wonder?
So decisive, so bold...
Look,
maybe it wasn't supposed to exist originally,
but it already does. Can't we just leave it?
Can't it stay?
Koto.
Just earlier you called this the thirteenth plane.
It's all connected.
The other twelve plane — everything.
Didn't we tell you that you did something crazy?
It's causing chain reactions everywhere!
No way...
Sis!
No...
Do you understand now?
This is the result of your playing house!
You abandoned your mission and twisted the world instead.
Did you think that was your job as an observer?
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Chapter
Twenty Four
Present (18)/ Koto
Head priest,
I'm grateful to you.
You overlooked my mistakes and helped when I had a problem.
While Shrine is a real pain,
I have the fox mask to thank for being able to raise Koto so well.
But I realized this.
Our work stretches beyond eternity, but...
When I found even a little bit of light...
Those who stood by my side meant more than anything.
Even if the cost was twisting the fabric of reality?
Head priest, even then, I feel no uncertainty.
I know what is most important to me.
Observer, do you honestly think you've become human?
Are you saying it's wrong
to want to love if you're not human?
This is nonsense.
Sheer stupidity.
What's wrong, A? Un?
Sensei!
Dear!
Koto!
Mom!
Koto?
Don't worry.
It's nothing serious.
You can't be serious!
What's going on?
Oh my, fireworks so early?
Your mother lost all her powers with your birth.
It would seem that you have inherited everything.
She is no longer truly real and can't exist outside the sanctuary anymore.
No good will come of making her strain herself.
Especially in this situation.
It's my fault...
I'm the reason Mom was confined to that place.
To think this was the result of your gallant search for a home.
How ironic.
You're wrong, Koto...
You're wrong.
You have no idea, Koto, how happy we were when you were born.
Koto!
It's all my fault...
No! Koto, look at me!
Koto!
It's my—
Oh, my!
Koto...
What are you doing?
It should take more than this to knock you off your feet.
Hey!
Your parents
are
alive
right there!
My parents and siblings by blood have been dead for ages!
Your parents are alive!
Stop standing there sulking, and do what you can while they're alive!
You awake now?
Remember, I've got something else I need you to do.
So I can't have you die here.
Yeah. You're right.
You're right.
I'll help you, so go convince that old guy!
Try harder this time. You weren't a bit of help with Mom, after all...
I suppose not...
Head priest!
I made up my mind.
If you don't help the people of the Mirror Capital and Mom, I'll break all the other planes as well.
I'm not sure that's...
All this will have been pointless if I let it end here!
So if there's no point, I'd rather just end everything.
So what's it gonna be, Shrine?
Sharp as a knife
I want to prove my own existence
Infinity stretches out around me and yet that is my safety line
Wanna take you high
The galaxy shines as you smile
I want to touch you
I don't want to listen to my punishments
Logic overwhelms me and I throw away reason
to sign up for this unreasonable risk game
I shine brightly thanks to expectations and pain
but I can't tell real and unreal apart
Fight with all your knowledge
So fight
Koto, you've really grown up.
You're my special daughter!
Frankly, it was a bit of an accident on my part that you were born.
I guess I haven't told you yet.
Let me tell you of my dream!
Let's Think of a Solution Together
Next time on Kyousougiga:
"Let's Think of a Solution Together".
I love you, my other me.