When was it again?
Sitting under a sky aglow with dusk,
our little boat lingered onward dreamily.
Children three nestled near with eager eye and willing ear.
Long has paled that sunny sky.
The echoes of their laughter and the memories of our joy
have all been slain by autumn frosts.
Where has she gone,
having rivaled the sun itself?
In a wonderland they lie, dreaming as the days go by.
Dreaming as the summers die.
Ever we drift down the stream, floating through its golden gleam.
Mirror Capital
Life, what is it but a dream?
CapitaL CraZe
Thus Spake Koto,
Our Protagonist
Come what may, I will have no regrets.
I believed, and made my decision.
I will move forward, taking pride in that.
As I always have, and I always will.
CHILDHOOD
I have to get going.
Okay.
You look so gloomy!
What a moody little brat!
Hey, now.
CENTRAL
AXIS
UNION
CENTRAL
AXIS
UNION
SHRINE
It won't be long.
Okay.
Thank you.
Watch the place while I'm gone, okay?
Okay.
Tell the priests if something happens, okay?
What else...
Count your tears, crybaby!
Inari won't be around to save you, wimp!
Stop it, you two.
Familiars aren't capable of ill-will.
Don't worry about what they say.
You're a member of the Shrine now. Keep your head held high,
Planetary Union
Shrine
no matter what they say.
Okay, Sensei.
So the child the Fox took in is one of us now?
How impudent.
It's a disgrace.
I have no idea what that Fox is thinking.
Who knows if that child is a human or a monster...
Those red eyes...
Don't skip your training.
Get stronger and face them head-on.
I'm sure that's what your mom would say, Koto.
Just do the best you can, shrimp!
We'll play with you when we get back.
Take care!
Though Sensei never spoke of her much,
I had a vague understanding that my mother was alive somewhere.
But, to navigate a life filled with many unpleasant adults,
as well as a handful of sympathetic ones, I think that knowledge was enough.
It's Koto, run!
Shouldn't we stop Koto-chan?
Koto!
Keep your arms closer to your body when you punch.
Okay!
There's something wrong with that student and her teacher!
These acts are not worthy of one who would wear the fox mask!
High Priest, I beg you to address this problem directly...
Inari! Koto!
You heard him, yes?
Yes! I think it's their fault for messing around during training.
And for not apologizing.
And for being weak.
Might I suggest you take a vacation?
I'll take care of your students while you're gone.
What?! No! No! No! No! I don't want you to do that, Sensei!
But this teacher is having doubts about his teaching methods.
No! No! No! No!
Someone has to lend him a hand.
This isn't about me!
In a wonderland they lie, dreaming as the days go by.
Good morning.
You're mumbling again.
What do you mean, mumbling?
You were thinking about the Mirror Capital again, huh?
I couldn't say.
Liar!
I know!
Ow!
That was a good kick. You put your weight into it.
I suppose I should praise you for training hard.
Of course!
I'm going to be number one at the Shrine!
The crybaby I knew sure has grown up.
As a teacher, I'm very proud.
I might end up being stronger than you.
I guess you'll be the teacher, then!
I want to go find Mom.
Yeah.
I want to meet her and talk to her.
I hope she's pretty.
Yeah.
I'm sure she'll be surprised.
I want to ask her about Dad, too.
Yeah.
But, Sensei, you already know the truth, right?
Koto,
I'm sure you'll make it there one day.
Where summer dies and is born anew.
Paradise lost.
The place beyond the mirror, where the gravestones of memories stand in neat rows.
I know you will.
Sensei, how are you?
I'm doing fine.
She's right there!
Get her!
Another ruckus again today.
Nice to see everyone's having fun.
Go on, dig in.
There are two types of people in this world.
Those who inconvenience me and those who don't.
Do you understand?
Ouch!
You little...
I'm having fun here in my own way,
but I really do want to see you and the others, Sensei.
I have no clue when I'll be able to return,
but one day, let's all be together.
To be continued!